[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":1194706,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":4319293,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub >6</sub> , you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":7278,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":4326575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2214,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":4328790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":6600,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":4335391,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1547,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":4336938,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":9483,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":4346422,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1232,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":4347655,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4416,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":4352071,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1218,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":4353289,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. I f the su m is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5443,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":4358732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1320,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":4360053,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3951,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":4364004,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1377,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":4365381,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3541,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":4368922,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1201,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":4370124,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br />< br /> (R emember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2734,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":4372859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1164,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":4374023,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5 ","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3880,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":4377903,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1037,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":4378941,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2294,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":4381235,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1068,"trial_type":"feed back","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":4382303,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":61648,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":4443952,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity  under +< sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":58886,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":4502839,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":126170,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":4629009,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1838,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":4630847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br  /> (Rem ember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3677,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":4634524,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1187,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":4635711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3376,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":4639087,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1140,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":4640227,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2584,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":4642811,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2010,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":4644821,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inv erse of  0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3466,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":4648287,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":6638,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":4654925,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, inverse is whgatever # that adds up to the 1st to make 6 = 0, unless its 0.","response_history":["yes","yee","yes, inverse is whgatever # that adds up to the 1st to make 6, n","yes, inverse is whgatever # that adds up to the 1st to make 6, unless its 0.","yes, inverse is whgatever # that adds up to the 1st to make 6 , unless its 0.","yes, inverse is whgatever # that adds up to the 1st to make 6 =, unless its 0.","yes, inverse is whgatever # that adds up to the 1st to make 6 = , unless its 0.","yes, inverse is whgatever # that adds up to the 1st to make 6 = 0, unless its 0."],"rt":43174,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":4698099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":83847,"trial_type":" instruct ions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":4781947,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":25872,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":4807819,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":62525,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":4870344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":8342,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":4878686,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":10917,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":4889603,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":79931,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":4969534,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4689,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":4974223,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":8718,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":4982942,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4084,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":4987026,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1625,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":4988651,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"i am trying to but this last generator part may be a bit too abstract for me.","response_history":["i am trying to but th ","i am trying to but this last generator part may be a p","i am trying to but this last generator part may be a bit too abstract for me."],"rt":184164,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":5172815,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new  operati on, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":54085,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":5226900,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":14170,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":5241070,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1145,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":5242215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13 -0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4046,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":5246262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":28339,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":5274601,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3085,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":5277687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2679,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":5280367,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2905,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":5283273,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. +9 on 4+1 is less than 9 so the sum stands instead of subtracting 9 from it","response_history":["5. +9 fuck","5. +9 fucnt","5. +9 fucn","5. +9 fuc","5. +9 fu","5. +9 f","5. +9 on 4+1 is less than 9 so the sum stands.","5. +9 on 4+1 is less than 9 so the sum stands instead of subtracting 9 from it"],"rt":34894,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":5318167,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13 -0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. sum of 8+4 is greater than 9, so subtract 9 from the sum.","response_history":["3. 8+4 is ","3. 8+4 is","3. 8+4 i","3. 8+4 ","3. 8+4","3. s8+4","3. su8+4","3. sum8+4","3. sum 8+4","3. sum o8+4","3. sum of8+4","3. sum of 8+4 is greater than 9, so subtract 9 from the sum."],"rt":23497,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":5341664,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"is it 0, the same as +6? i dont think i can explain it in words very well. ","response_history":["is it 0, the same as +6? i dont think i can explain it in words. ","is it 0, the same as +6? i dont think i can explain it in  words.","is it 0, the same as +6? i dont think i can explain it in words very well. "],"rt":56767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":5398432,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4641,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":5403073,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":3714,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":5406788,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6, the  number added to 3 to get to 9, which would make the function +9 subtract from to make 0.","response_history":["6, a","6, w","6, the number added to 3 to get to 9, which would make the function +9 subtract to make 0.","6, the number added to 3 to get to 9, which would make the function +9 subtract fr make 0.","6, the number added to 3 to get to 9, which would make the function +9 subtract fro make 0.","6, the number added to 3 to get to 9, which would make the function +9 subtract from make 0.","6, the number added to 3 to get to 9, which would make the function +9 subtract from  make 0.","6, the number added to 3 to get to 9, which would make the function +9 subtract from t make 0.","6, the number added to 3 to get to 9, which would make the function +9 subtract from to make 0."],"rt":39036,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":5445824,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain i n words  how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"i dont think that 2 is a generator under +9,. it wasn't a generator under +6 if i recall correctly. ","response_history":["i dont think tht","i dont think that 2 is a gereator","i dont think that 2 is a genreator","i dont think that 2 is a genereator","i dont think that 2 is a generator under +9,. it was ","i dont think that 2 is a generator under +9,. it wasn't a generaa","i dont think that 2 is a generator under +9,. it wasn't a generator under +6. ","i dont think that 2 is a generator under +9,. it wasn't a generator under +6.","i dont think that 2 is a generator under +9,. it wasn't a generator under +6 if i recall correctly. "],"rt":610978,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":6056802,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"fr ee","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, because i dont think that 3 can make all the numbers between 0-8 with +9.","response_history":["no, because i dont think h","no, because i dont think that 3 can make all the numbers between 0-8 with +9."],"rt":153927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":6210729,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"i dont think that 5 is a generator under +9 because it doesnt make every number 0-8","response_history":["i dnot","i dno","i dn","i dont think that 5 is a generator under +9 becasue ","i dont think that 5 is a generator under +9 becasue","i dont think that 5 is a generator under +9 becasu","i dont think that 5 is a generator under +9 becas","i dont think that 5 is a generator under +9 becaui","i dont think  that 5  is a generator under +9 because it doesnt make every number 0-8"],"rt":126364,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":6337093,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"i dont think that 6 is a generator under +9 because it doesnt make every number 0-8","response_history":["i dont think that 5 is a generator under +9 because it doesnt make every number 0-8","i dont think that 6 is a generator under +9 because it doesnt make every number 0-8"],"rt":36922,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":6374016,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think  of. If  you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":4798,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":6378815,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+x?","response_history":["1+x?"],"rt":73204,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":6452019,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know how to explain a +n formula ","response_history":[" am so confuse, sorry. ","I am so confuse, sorry. ","I am so conf uses, so rry. ","I am so confuse, sorry. ","I am so confused, sorry. ","I am so confused , sorry. ","I am so confused h, sorry. ","I am so confused he, sorry. ","I am so confused her, sorry. ","I am so confused here, sorry.  ","I am so confused here, sorry. T ","I am so confused here, sorry. Th ","I am so confused here, sorry. The  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The + ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n i ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is k ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is ki ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is kil ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is kill ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killi ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killin ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killine  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killine m ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killine me ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killine m ","I am s o confused here, sorry. The +n is killine  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killine ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killin ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing m ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I w ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wou ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I woul ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I would ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn' ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't o ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't ow  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wo uldn't o w o ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't ow ow  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't ow ow t ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't ow ow to  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't ow ow to e ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't ow ow to ex ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't ow ow to expl ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't kow ow to expl ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know ow to expl ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know how to expl ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know how to expla ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know how to explai ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know how to explain  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The  +n is ki lling me I wouldn't know how to explain a  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know how to explain a + ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know how to explain a +n  ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know how to explain a +n f ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know how to explain a +n for ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know how to explain a +n form ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know how to explain a +n formu ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know how to explain a +n formul ","I am so confused here, sorry. The +n is killing me I wouldn't know how to explain a +n formula "],"rt":69080,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":6521099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generat ors? How  can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I could not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations per +6, +9/ ","response_history":["I donthink i came","I d","I cont come up w","I did not come up withpar","I did not come up withpa","I did not come up withp","I did not come up with a pattern before;  jut ","I did not come up with a pattern before;  jut","I did not come up with a pattern before;  ju","I did not come up with a pattern before;  j","I did not come up with a pattern before;  ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I justy","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went though ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went though","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went thoug=","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went th oug","I  did not come up with a pattern before; I just went thou","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went tho","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went throughseveral ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several  ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several d ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several di ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several dif ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several diff ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several diffe ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several differ ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several differe ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several differen ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different  ","I did not come up with a  pattern  before; I just went through several different n ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different nu ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different num ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different numb ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different numbe ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number  ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number c ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number co ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number com ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number comb ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combi ","I did not come up with a pattern befo re; I ju st went through several different number combin ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combina ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinat ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinati ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinatio ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combination ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations  ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations p ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations pe ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations per  ","I did not come up with a  pattern  before; I just went through several different number combinations per + ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations per +6 ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations per +6,  ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations per +6, + ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations per +6, +9 ","I did not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations per +6, +9/ ","I c not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations per +6, +9/ ","I cou not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations per +6, +9/ ","I coul not come up with a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations per +6, +9/ ","I could not c ome up w ith a pattern before; I just went through several different number combinations per +6, +9/ "],"rt":97697,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":6618797,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4781,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":6623579,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5161,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":6628741,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not  a gener ator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":7688,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":6636429,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I am sorry I do not understand the generator portion of this exercise well enough to explain it.","response_history":["I am sorry I do not understant","I am sorry I do not understand the or gejdfsha;j","I am sorry I do not understand the enerator","I am sorry I do not understand the generator portion of this exercise well enough to explain it."],"rt":51129,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":6687560,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":6022,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":6693582,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I am sorry, I do not understand the generator portion of this HIT and I couldnt begin to explain the above.","response_history":["I am sorry, I don ","I am sorry, I don","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator poorttttion ","I am  sorry,  I do not understand the generator po","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator p","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator ","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator","I am sorry, I do not understand the generatotionr","I am sorry, I do not understand the generatotion","I am sorry, I do not understand the generatotio","I am sorry, I do not understand the generatoti","I am sorry, I do not understand the generatot","I am sorry, I do not understand the generato","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator portion of this HIT t","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator portion of this HIT ","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator portion of this HIT and I couldnt explain the above.","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator portion of this HIT and I couldnt bexplain the above.","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator portion of this HIT and I couldnt beexplain the above.","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator portion of this  HIT and  I couldnt begexplain the above.","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator portion of this HIT and I couldnt begiexplain the above.","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator portion of this HIT and I couldnt beginexplain the above.","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator portion of this HIT and I couldnt begin explain the above.","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator portion of this HIT and I couldnt begin texplain the above.","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator portion of this HIT and I couldnt begin toexplain the above.","I am sorry, I do not understand the generator portion of this HIT and I couldnt begin to explain the above."],"rt":61539,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":6755122,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":3501,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":6758624,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2001,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":6760626,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"34","response_history":["34"],"rt":2551,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":6763178,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some  graduate  school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":28924,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":6792102,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"high school calculus, and in college math for social sciences.","response_history":["cqa","cq","c","high school calc","high school cal","high school calculus, and in college math for social sciences."],"rt":22388,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":6814492,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never  heard of  it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5369,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":6819862,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":3652,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":6823514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do y ou feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2859,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":6826374,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2753,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":6829128,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3080,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":6832208,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2771,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":6834980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English/spanish","response_history":["English/spanish"],"rt":7295,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":6842276,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, but i should have for the generator portion","response_history":["no, but i should  have fo r the genator portion","no, but i should have for the geneator portion","no, but i should have for the generator portion"],"rt":17223,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":6859499,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"the first two parts were easy to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator portion on. I also could not understand the abstract portion of the +n questions.","response_history":["the first two pparts were easy to understand","the first two parts were easy to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator portion on. I coould not ","the first two parts were easy to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator portion on. I could not ","the first two parts were easy to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator por tion on.  I acould not ","the first two parts were easy to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator portion on. I alcould not ","the first two parts were easy to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator portion on. I alscould not ","the first two parts were easy to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator portion on. I alsocould not ","the first two parts were easy to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator portion on. I also could not undertsa","the first two parts were easy to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator portion on. I also could not underts","the first two parts were easy to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator portion on. I also could not undert","the first two parts were easy to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator portion on. I also could not understand the absr","the first two parts w ere easy  to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator portion on. I also could not understand the abstracrt","the first two parts were easy to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator portion on. I also could not understand the abstracr","the first two parts were easy to understand, +6 and the inverse, but I got lost from the generator portion on. I also could not understand the abstract portion of the +n questions."],"rt":69996,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":6929496,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]